(忆往昔)
你是说  天启就要来了
Are you saying that this is the...Apocalypse?
那这些具体的前兆  预示了什么
And these specific omens -- they're prelude to what?
天启四骑士
The Four Horsemen.
骑红马的是哪一个
And which one rides the red horse?
战争
War.
在这镇上肆虐的  是饥荒
This town is suffering from Famine.
饥荒骑士
A-as in the Horseman?
好极了
Great.
死亡骑士要降临于世
The angel of death must be brought into this world
必须经由残忍地屠杀
through a place of awful carnage.
你好啊  死亡骑士
Hello, Death.
鲍比  她是谁
Bobby, who is that?
我妻子
She's my wife.
世界末日就要来了
It's the end of the world.
而且如果我不阻止它并且救下所有人
And if I don't stop it and save everyone,
就没有人能救我们了  我们都得死
then no one will, and we all die.
我只是太累了  兄弟
I'm just tired, man.
我受够了
I'm done.
真的受够了
I am just done.
帮帮我
I need some help.
(如今)
(克莱·詹姆斯·汤姆森之墓)
热带草原上  角马正在休憩
Here on the savanna, the wildebeest lounges,
慵懒而满足
lazy and self-content...
对从阴影中悄然靠近的凶猛肉食动物
And oblivious to the fierce predator
丝毫没有察觉
that stalks him from the shadows.
庞大的角马群向南迁徙  寻找水源
Great wildbeest herds migrate south, searching for water
尽可能多地饮水  为漫长旱季的来临做准备
drinking their field prepairation for the long dry season to come.
靠近兽群边缘的角马
... the wildbeests arround edge.
惊怕每一丝风吹草动
every movement, every sound of potential attact.
灌木丛中的一阵轻响
Mere as a rush of wind in the bushes
也能让整个角马群乱成一团
can send the entire herd into a bone-crashing snap.
开始的时候角马会被迷惑  四散奔逃
At first the animal reacts with confusion, and then...
当疲惫的猎物再次回到饮水处
When the beast returns wearily to its watering hole.
捕猎者已绕到它的背后
The killer's right behind it.
它发起攻击之时  速度极快
When it attacks, it attacks quickly.
不
No.
求你  上帝啊  不
Please! God! No!
[邪恶力量 第5季第15集]
鲍比  听着  收到留言回电话
Bobby, listen, when you get this message, call!
好吗
Okay?
他还是不在家
Is he still not home?
他坐轮椅能走多远
How far could he get in that chair?
我们现在怎么办
So, what do we do?
看来  只能自己办了
Well...guess we just do it ourselves.
韦尔斯先生  给我们讲讲事情经过吧
Mr. Wells, why don't you tell us what you saw --
用你自己的话
in your own words.
-叫我迪格(挖掘者)  - 迪格
- Call me Digger.  - Digger?
谁给你取的这名字啊
Who -- who gave you that name?
我自己
I did.
你自己给自己起别名
You gave yourself your own nickname?
这不允许啊
You can't do that.
你管太宽了吧
Who died and made you queen?
好了  还是讲讲你看到了什么吧
Okay. Uh, why don't you just tell us what you saw?
我看见克莱·汤姆森从窗户
I saw Clay Thompson climb into Benny Sutton's trailer
爬进了本尼·萨顿的房车
through the window.
几分钟以后  克莱走了出来
Couple minutes later, Clay walked out,
而本尼死了
and Benny's dead.
那么
And, uh...
你看到的是这个人吗
...is this the guy you saw?
他当时浑身是泥  不过是他
Well, he was all covered with mud, but, yeah.
就是克莱
That's Clay.
你知道克莱·汤姆森五年前就死了吧
And you are aware that Clay Thompson died five years ago?
知道
Yep.
你确定你看到的是他吗
And you're positive that it was this guy.
你是说我在撒谎吗
You calling me a liar?
没有  当然没有
No, no, no. Of course not.
听着
Look.
你能想到克莱·汤姆森
Can you think of any reason why Clay Thompson --
不论他是死是活
alive or dead --
有什么理由要杀本尼·萨顿吗
would want to kill Benny Sutton?
当然能
Hell, yeah.
五年前
Well, five years ago,
正是本尼杀死了克莱
Benny's the one that killed Clay in the first place.
是吗
Is that a fact?
是  所谓的"狩猎意外"
Well, yeah, so-called "Hunting accident."
现在  要我说
Now, if you ask me...
就是克莱从坟墓里爬出来报仇了
Clay came back from the grave to get a little payback.
继续
Go on.
欧文  把蛋糕放下  去拿个苹果吃
Owen, put down the cupcake and pick up an apple.
好不好
Okay?
乖  我爱你
Okay. I love you.
注意了
Heads up.
《冰血暴》
"Fargo."
迪格
Digger.
治安官
Sheriff.
先生们
Gentlemen.
我是乔迪·米尔斯治安官
I'm sheriff Jody Mills.
我想我们没见过面吧
I don't believe we've had the pleasure.
多尔夫曼和尼德梅尔探员
Agents Dorfman and Neidermeyer.
联邦调查局
FBI
先生们  欢迎来到苏瀑镇
Welcome to Sux Falls, gentlemen.
可以问问你们找迪格做什么吗
Can I ask you what you're doing with Digger here?
他们在工作
They're doing their job.
他们相信我  治安官
They believe me... sheriff.
联调局相信死人会杀人
The FBI believes a dead man committed a murder?
治安官  我们只是问几个问题而已
Look, we're just asking a few questions, sheriff.
仅此而已
That's all.
如果死人没杀人
Of course, if a dead man didn't commit the murder,
那是谁杀的呢
then, uh, who did?
二位来此有何公干
What'd you say your jurisdiction here was again?
我们来此
Our jurisdiction is
执行联邦政府分派的任务
wherever the United States government sends us.
是嘛  让我和你们的长官
Oh, yeah. How 'bout me and your supervisor
谈谈如何
have a little chat about that?
没问题
Absolutely.
我是威利斯探员
Agent Willis speaking.
威利斯探员  我是乔迪·米尔斯治安官
Agent Willis, this is sheriff Jody Mills --
鲍比
Bobby?
您说什么
Excuse me?
你是鲍比·辛格吧
Is this Bobby Singer?
听着  我不认识您说的这个人  但是
Listen, I don't know who this is, but...
我是联邦调查局的汤姆·威利斯探员
this is agent Tom Willis of the FBI.
扯淡
Bull crap.
联邦调查局是吧
FBI, huh?
那么
So, uh...
看来你认识鲍比·辛格
so you know Bobby Singer?
这真是太巧了
That is...a fun coincidence.
我对鲍比·辛格的印象就是
Here's what I know about Bobby Singer.
他是个危险分子
He's a menace around here --
一个不守规矩的酒鬼大混蛋
ass-full of drunk-and-disorderlies
还涉嫌邮件诈骗
and mail fraud.
明白了吗
You understanding me?
我们一致认为
I think we all can agree
您已经讲得很清楚了
you've made yourself perfectly clear, yes.
所以  无论你们三个在预谋什么
So, whatever the three of you are planning,
给我马上停止
it ends here -- now.
明白了吗  探员们
Ten-four on that, agents?
明白
Yeah.
你知道我们打过多少次电话了吗
You know how many times we called?
你到哪儿去了
Where have you been?
练习轮椅杂技
Playing murderball.
这什么味道啊
What's that smell?
香皂吗
Is that soap?
你打扫卫生来着吗
Did you clean?
你以为你是我妈啊
What are you, my mother?
要你管
Bite me!
鲍比  认真点
Bobby, seriously.
我一直在工作
I've been working.
想办法阻止那个恶魔
You know, trying to find a way to stop the devil.
-有进展吗  - 你觉得呢
- Find anything?  - What do you think?
鲍比  只是
Bobby, it's just...
有个案子
there's a case
就发生在你家不到五英里的地方
less than five miles from your house.
本尼·萨顿那案子吗
What, the -- the Benny Sutton thing?
就为了这事儿吗
That's what this is about?
你老早就知道这事
You knew about this?
废话  当然了  我早就做过调查了
Hell, yes. I checked into it already.
没什么不正常的啊
There's nothing here.
有目击者看见一个死人杀了人还叫正常啊
Except a witness who saw a dead guy commit murder.
什么目击者  迪格·韦尔斯
What witness? Digger Wells?
是他  怎么了
Yeah. So?
他就是个酒鬼
So, he's a drunk.
那怎么解释那场雷雨
Well, what about the lightning storms?
那个看似是恶鬼出现的前兆
They look like omens.
在二月这很常见
Except in February
南达科塔正处在雷雨季
in South Dakota in storm season.
伙计们  开始我也以为另有隐情
Guys, I thought it was something, too.
有时候事情就是这么简单
Sometimes a cigar is just a cigar.
那究竟谁杀了那家伙
So who killed the guy?
谁都可能啊
Take your pick.
本尼·萨顿已经混蛋到一定程度了
This Benny Sutton guy was a grade-a son of a bitch.
他这么混蛋不是一天两天了
There's a list of the living a year long
大家都想给他点颜色看看
wouldn't mind putting a cap in his ass.
就是说你觉得这案子没什么异常
So, you're telling us... nothing?
很遗憾
Sorry.
看来你们这次是白来一趟了
Looks like you wasted a tank of gas on this one.
好吧
All right.
怎么了
What's up?
这不就是那个墓地吗
Isn't that the graveyard back there?
是又怎么了  鲍比早就查过了
Yeah. So what? Bobby already checked it out.
那又怎样呢  鲍比就不会出错啊
And? What, Bobby's never wrong?
我们过去看一眼  然后就上路
Come on. We'll take a peek, and then we'll hit the road.
没什么损失吧
Can't hurt.
看看这
Hey.
你觉得这是新挖开的吗
That look fresh to you?
绝对的
Yeah, actually.
到底怎么回事
What is going on here?
说不好  但绝对不是什么好事
I don't know, but something stinks.
别开枪  拜托了
Don't shoot me! Please!
钱都放在保险柜里
There's money in the safe.
我们不稀罕你的钱
We don't want your money.
那你们想要什么
What do you want?
什么都行  请别伤害我
Anything. Please...
你是克莱·汤姆森  对吗
You're Clay Thompson, right?
你们是谁
Who are you?
联邦调查局
FBI.
FBI?
天啊  你们是为本尼那事来的
Oh, my god. This is about Benny.
本尼怎么了
Wha-- what about Benny?
他杀了我  他在我背后开枪
He killed me! He shot me in the back!
我就不应该让他尝点苦头吗
I'm supposed to let him get away with that?
等等  你是在认罪吗
Hold up. Are -- are you confessing?
拜托了  我会跟你们走  别吵醒我的孩子
Please. I'll go with you. Just -- just don't wake my kids.
你打算跟我们去哪
Y-you'll go with us where?
监狱
Jail.
让我先搞搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
你是克莱·汤姆森  五年前就死了
You're Clay Thompson, and you died five years ago?
-是的  - 三天前
- Yes.  - And three days ago
你从坟墓里爬出来
you climbed out of your grave...
-杀了本尼·萨顿  - 是的
- And you killed Benny Sutton?  - Yes.
-那么其实你已经是死人了  - 差不多吧
- So you are, in fact, a dead guy.  - I guess.
我也说不清我是什么
I-I-I don't know what I am.
克莱
Clay?
我报警了
I called 911.
亲爱的别担心  这些人是联邦调查局的
It's okay, honey. These men are the FBI.
他们是为了本尼的事来的
They're here about Benny.
汤姆森先生  你还是最好
Why don't you come with us, Mr. Thompson?
跟我们走一趟吧
I think that'd be best.
迪恩
Dean.
他是个怪物
He's a monster.
他就是个普通人
He's a soccer dad.
那你想拿他怎么办
What do you want to do with him?
不许动
Freeze!
放下枪
Drop your guns!
哇  好的
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. All right. Hey.
还记得你说的那个
Remember the guy you said that was dead
不可能杀人的死人吗
and couldn't possibly commit murder?
他就在那里
There he is.
那又怎样
And?
"那又怎样"
"And"?
那就请你
And you're welcome --
拿下这个活生生的僵尸杀手
for catching the undead killer zombie.
不管他是不是
Whatever he is or isn't --
你们都没有权利在大街上
that don't give you the right to shoot him.
-向他开枪  - 向我开枪
- In the middle of the street.  - Shoot me?
-汤姆森先生 你可以走了  - 放他走
- You're free to go, Mr. Thompson  - Free to go?!
真不敢相信你们要杀我
I can't believe you were gonna kill me.
-你是个僵尸  - 我是纳税人
- You're a zombie!  - I'm a taxpayer!
怎么着  治安官受贿啦
So, what? Sheriff's on the take?
是的  没有
Yeah. No.
僵尸们向她行贿么
The zombies are paying her off?
他们现在是朋友啦
So, what? Now they're friends?
鲍比  那治安官不是讨厌你吗
Bobby, I thought the sheriff hated you?
是的  直到5天前
She did till five days ago.
5天前发生了什么
What happened five days ago?
镇子里的死人们都复活了
The dead started rising all over town.
那你早就知道了
So you knew about this?
是的
Yep.
我想萨姆的意思是  你骗了我们
I think what Sam meant to say is, you lied to us?
听着  我告诉过你们这案子没什么异常
Look -- I told you there was nothing here.
对你们而言就是没有
And there isn't. Not for you.
这儿可有僵尸
There are zombies here.
万物皆有其根源
There's zombies... and then there's zombies.
跟我来
Come with me.
你能不能说清楚到底...
You want to tell us what the hell --
嘿
Oh, hey.
我没想到你会带朋友回来
I didn't realize you were bringing company.
宝贝  现在是凌晨4点  你不用做饭的
It's 4 a.m., babe. You didn't need to cook.
我再去拿些碟子
Oh, please I'll get some more plates.
她是谁
Who was that?
凯伦  我妻子
Karen. My wife.
你新找的啊
Your new wife?
我死去的妻子
My dead wife.
辛格夫人  这太美味了
This is incredible, Mrs. Singer.
谢谢  迪恩
Thank you, Dean.
咋啦  就是好吃呀
What? It is.
很好  凯伦  谢谢
It's great, Karen. Thanks.
你能让我们单独呆一会么
Could you, um, just give us a minute?
你疯了吗  到底怎么回事
Are you crazy? What the hell?
迪恩  我可以解释
Dean, I can explain.
解释什么  骗我们
Explain what? Lying to us?
还是那个美国僵尸女孩在你的厨房做蛋糕
Or the American girl zombie making cupcakes in your kitchen?!
首先  那是我妻子  所以尊重点
First of all, that's my wife, so watch it.
鲍比  不管那东西是什么  那不是你妻子
Bobby, whatever that thing is in there, it is not your wife.
你怎么知道
And how do you know that?
还用说吗
Are you serious?
孩子  你觉得我是傻子吗
You think I'm an idiot, boy?
我死去的妻子出现在我家门口
My dead wife shows up on my doorstep,
我当然会尽我所学去测试她
I'm not gonna test her every way I ever learned?
那它是什么  僵尸  亡魂
So what is it? Zombies? Revenant?
我哪知道
Hell if I can tell.
她没有伤疤或是伤口
She's got no scars, no wounds,
对盐  银具和圣水都没反应
no reaction to salt, silver, holy water...
鲍比  她可是从棺材里爬出来的
Bobby, she crawled out of her coffin.
不  她没有  我把她火化的
No, she didn't. I cremated her.
不知怎么回事  她回来了
Somehow, some way, she's back.
那是不可能的
That's impossible.
还用你说
Tell me about it.
你埋葬了她的骨灰
You bury her ashes?
-是的  - 埋哪儿了
- Yeah.  - Where?
在墓地
In the cemetery.
他们都是在那里复活的
That's where they all rose from.
-多少个  - 15或者20个
- How many? - 15, 20.
我列了张表
I made a list.
有凯伦
Uh, there's Karen...
克莱
Clay...
米尔斯治安官
Sheriff Mills --
她儿子复活了
her little boy came back.
没有任何迹象或是前兆吗
And there were no signs? No omens?
那时候下过雷雨
Well, there were the lightning storms.
我们早说过了  还有什么
That's what we said. What else?
"火焰之中  一匹白马屹立于我面前"
"And through the fire stood before me a pale horse.
"他坐在马背之上  手持镰刀"
"And he that sat atop him carried a scythe,
"我目睹自他复活之后"
"and I saw since he had risen,
"他们也将复活"
"they, too, shall rise,
"自他而生  因他而生"
and from him and through him."
怎么  是死亡骑士在作怪吗
So, what, death is behind this?
死亡骑士  那种拿着镰刀的骷髅死神吗
Deah, like "Grim Reaper" Death?
是的
Yeah.
真棒
Awesome.
又一个天启骑士
Another horseman.
肯定是星期四
Must be Thursday.
鲍比
Bobby...
为什么死亡骑士要在苏福尔斯这种
Why would Death raise 15 people
偏僻小镇复活15个人
in a podunk town like Sioux Falls?
我不知道
I don't know.
如果真是死亡骑士在作怪
You know, if death is behind this,
不论他的目的何在
then whatever these things are...
反正肯定没好事
it's not good.
你要理解我们的职责所在
You know what we have to do here.
她什么都不记得了
She doesn't remember anything, you know.
什么意思
What do you mean?
不记得曾被恶魔附身
Being possessed,
而我杀了她
me killing her...
之后再复活
her coming back.
鲍比
Bobby...
别摆出这种表情
No, no, don't "Bobby" Me.
什么都别说了
Just...
听听这声音
just listen, okay?
她哼着歌做饭
She hums when she cooks.
以前
She always...
她做饭时总是哼歌
used to hum when she cooked.
虽然跑调严重  但是...
Tone deaf as all hell, but...
我从没想过能再次听到
And I never thought I would hear it again.
启示录上说
Look, just read revelation.
死者会在天启时复活
The -- the dead rise during the apocalypse.
但这又不一定是坏事
There's nothing in there that says that's bad!
也许是因为当下形势如此糟糕
Hell, maybe it's the one good thing
而唯独此事振奋人心  这不是很好吗
That comes out of this whole bloody mess.
换作你的话会怎么做
And what would you do if you were us?
我当然知道
I know what I'd do.
也知道你们的想法
And I know what you think you got to do.
但是
But...
我求你们了
I'm begging you.
求求你们
Please.
拜托
让她留下
Leave her be.
你有何想法
So, what do you think?
没什么想法
There's nothing to think about.
我可不会让鲍比独自在家
I'm not gonna leave Bobby at home
和他的僵尸新娘共处一室
with the bride of Frankenstein.
那你想怎样
Then what do you want to do?
就这样当着鲍比的面  爆头了她的头吗
Just walk in there in front of Bobby and blow her skull off?
要是她想对鲍比下手
If she decides that Bobby's face
老子还真干得出来
is the blue plate special, I'd like to be there.
好吧
Fine.
看看还有什么线索
See what else we can find out.
我吓到你了吗
Oops. Did I scare you?
没有
No. No. No.
你没什么吓人的
There's...nothing scary about you at all.
想吃点午餐吗
Feel like some lunch?
不用了  谢谢
Uh...I'm good. Thanks.
来吧  派还多着呢
Come On. There's more pie.
我觉得鲍比不想让我进去
I don't think that Bobby wants me inside.
那就当是咱俩的秘密嘛
Guess it'll have to be our secret, then, huh?
来吧
Come on.
不用说我也知道  你肯定超喜欢派
I'm gonna go out on a limb and guess that you like pies.
全是你烤的吗
Did you bake all these?
我也不知道为什么
I don't know what it is.
回来之后就一直烤
Since I got back, I can't stop baking.
你睡过觉吗
Yeah, when do you have time to sleep?
我不睡
I don't.
肯定是太兴奋了
Must be the excitement.
也可能是因为死了
Or being dead.
我知道你不信任我
I know you don't trust me.
为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
省省吧  迪恩
Come on, dean.
所以你才过来吧
That's why you're here, isn't it?
为了监视我
Keeping an eye on me?
我知道你的身份
I know who you are.
我也知道  鲍比变了
Just like I know Bobby's not the same
不再像我当初嫁给他那时  温和而唠叨
mild-mannered scrap dealer I married.
你们猎鬼
You hunt things.
而我就是个鬼
I-I'm a thing.
我知道
I get it.
所以你也应该知道
So then you know that Sam and I
我和萨姆不会放任鲍比不管
Would never let anything happen to Bobby.
他就像我们的父亲
That he's like a father to us.
我明白
I understand.
有你们照顾他真好  迪恩
And he's lucky to have you looking out for him, dean.
但不只有你们关心他
But you're not the only one.
就这样吗
Is that so?
我记得一清二楚
I-I remember everything, you know.
我死时的感觉
When I died.
那恶魔占了我的身体
That demon taking over my body...
还有在它控制下我的所作所为
And the things it made me do.
鲍比别无选择  只能...
And Bobby having no choice but to...
你也知道他做了什么
Well, you know what he did.
但我明白他的眼神
But I can see it in his eyes when he looks at me.
饱含内疚之情
The guilt.
折磨着他
It weighs on him.
你为什么不告诉他真相呢
So why don't you just tell him you remember?
不用你说我也知道
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
你从未有过真正的爱情
and say you've never been in love.
他是我丈夫
He's my husband.
我希望他平静生活
My job is to bring him peace...
远离痛苦
Not pain.
琼斯太太在吗
Mrs. Jones?!
埃兹拉·琼斯?
Ezra jones?
你是埃兹拉·琼斯吗
Um...Ezra jones?
怎么了
W-what is it?
我就站在这儿  你说吧
You think maybe you could tell me from here?
好吧  肯定没啥好事儿
Yeah. I'm gonna regret this.
小点声  凯伦在楼上
Keep your damn voices down. Karen's upstairs.
抱歉  现在形势紧迫
Oh, I'm sorry. We're a little tense right now.
琼斯老太太是谁
Who's old lady Jones?
-她第一个复活  - 所以也第一个露出真面目
- The first one to come up. - First one to go bad.
-她总是疯疯癫癫的  - 怎么个疯法
- Ah, she was always a nutty broad. - Nutty how?
疯到吃掉她老公的内脏吗
Nutty like the way she ate her husband's stomach?
她活着时不会这么疯狂吧
Was that the level of nutty she was in life?
是没错
No.
鲍比  我能理解你
Look, Bobby, I feel for you.
但是你必须认清
But you have got to acknowledge
你被蒙蔽了双眼
That you're not exactly seeing this straight!
不管你承认与否
Bobby, whether you admit it or not,
这些僵尸在变异
These things are turning.
我们得阻止他们所有人
We have to stop them -- all of them.
-你们走吧  - 什么
- Time to go.  - What?
没听见吗  别管我的事
You heard me. Off my property.
不然呢  你就开枪吗
Or what? You'll shoot?
如果凯伦变异了  我自会处理
If Karen turns, I will handle it --
我说了算
My way.
这很危险
This is dangerous.
我不会再说第二遍
I'm not telling you twice.
他疯了
He's crazy.
那可是他妻子  迪恩
It's his wife, dean.
那就和我们倒戈相向吗?!
So he goes "Full metal jacket" On us?
至于嘛  我们可是他的家人  萨姆
We're his family, sam.
听着  老哥  还有更要紧的事
Look, man. Bigger fish, okay?
现在有一大堆僵尸
I mean, we got a bunch of zombies
准备把这镇上的活人都啃光呢
About to turn this town into a giant chew toy.
就是  他和其中一个共处一室
Yeah, and he's alone in the house
欢乐地做着点心派
making pie with one of 'em!
-那又怎样  - 你还问我
- All right? So?  - So!
我要回去
I'm gonna have to go back there
去杀了她
And -- and -- and kill her.
我只能想到这点
That's the only thing I can think of.
要是让他看到  你就死定了
If he sees you, you're a dead man.
那就别让他看到
Well, then, I guess I won't let him see me.
好吧
Okay.
那我去镇上
I'll...head to town
把镇民救出来  应该不难
And rescue everyone -- should be easy.
听着简单
Sounds like.
我要些援助
I'm gonna need some help.
治安官怎样
What about the sheriff?
按之前的经验
Uh, last time I checked,
那治安官还帮着僵尸呢
The sheriff was pretty pro-zombie.
那你得说服她咯
Well, I guess you'll just have to convince her.
-怎么个说法   - 我咋知道
- How?  - I don't know.
你就去呗
You're just gonna.
好点了吗  宝贝儿
There. Does that feel better, honey?
我很饿  妈咪
I'm so hungry, mommy.
我知道
Oh, I know. I know.
我给你煮些汤吧
Mommy's gonna make you some soup, okay?
好
Okay.
我不知道还能怎么说  大夫
I don't know what else to tell you, Doc.
我们都量3次体温了
We checked the thermometer three times.
体温是44°C
His temperature is 111 degrees.
-妈咪  - 等等  大夫
- Mommy.  - Hold on, doc.
-我饿  - 给他吃点这个吧
- I'm hungry!  - Can you take that in to him?
德怀特医生  我是乔迪·米尔斯
Dr. Dwight, it's Jody Mills.
凯伦  别待在窗边
Karen, stay away from the windows.
凯伦
Karen?
Karen?!
克伦
Karen?
-我没事  - 还好吧
- I'm okay.  - Yeah?
我没事
I'm okay.
我只是
I just...
我没事
I'm okay.
我只是有点头晕
I-I just got to be dizzy.
你发烧了
You're burning up.
我没事
Oh, I'm okay.
我得去找点吃的
I-I just need something to eat.
我会没事的  真的
And I'll be fine. Really.
我不知道怎么解释  医生
I don't know how to explain it, doctor.
所以我们才找你  我...
That's -- that's why we're calling you. I...
肖恩
Sean?
欧文
Owen?
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
-快跑  - 不
- Let's go!  - No!
跑
Go!
-我丈夫  - 别管了  他死了
- My husband!  - Leave it! He's dead!
-那不是我儿子  - 没错  他不是
- That was not my son!  - You're right. It wasn't.
听着  治安官  整个小镇危在旦夕
Listen, sheriff. Your town is in danger.
所有人都有危险
People are in danger,
我们得救他们
And we need to help them now.
你能帮我吗
Can you do that for me?
能集中注意力吗  治安官
Can you focus for me, sheriff?
治安官
Sheriff?
怎么收拾他们
How do we put them down?
直接爆头
Head shot.
我们需要武器
We're gonna need weapons.
先四处去找人
We can start by rounding up everybody we can find.
有没有安全的地方来安顿大家
Where is there a safe place we can take people?
监狱
Jail.
好
Right.
那个...
Just, um...
先等我一下
Give me a minute.
我很饿  鲍比
I'm so hungry, Bobby.
我这就去给你煮点东西吃
I'll fix you something to eat...in a minute.
我能感觉到不对劲
I can feel it. It's happening.
会没事的
Is it gonna be right.
不
No.
才不是
It's not.
我在变异  鲍比
I'm turning, Bobby.
你心里清楚
You know I am.
没事的
It's okay.
-动手吧  - 不行
- Do it.  - No way.
-求你了  - 不
- Please.  - No.
我记得
I remember.
记得什么
You remember what?
我的遭遇
Everything.
我被那个恶魔附身
The demon inside me.
而你亲手杀了我
You killing me.
我都历历在目
I remember.
那你更应该明白
Then you know...
这种痛苦  我不想再经历一次
Why I can't do it again.
我还记得一些其他事情
I remember something else, too.
我复活时
When I came back...
看到一个男人
There was a man.
什么男人
What do you mean, a man?
就在墓地那里
At the grave.
他是那么的削瘦
He was so thin.
简直是一具骨架
Like a skeleton.
他让我给你带句话
And he told me to give you a message.
给我吗
Me?
为什么不早点告诉我呢
W-why didn't you tell me this before?
你已不堪重负
You've seen so much.
我只是
I just...
我只是想要你微笑依旧
I just wanted to see you smile.
他说了什么
What was the message?
怎么了  鲍比
Bobby?!
各位  你们人手一枪  要是看见活死人
All right, if I hand you a gun and you see a dead person,
不论他是你的朋友也好
I don't care if it's your friend,
邻居或是你的妻子也罢
Your neighbor, or your wife,
直接爆头
You shoot for the head.
只有这样我们才能活命
That's the only way we survive.
你就不向大家自我介绍下吗
Uh, you mind telling us who the hell you are?
我是鲍比·辛格的朋友
Friend of Bobby Singer's.
就那个市井醉汉吗
Town drunk.
不  我以为...
No, I-I thought...
他现在戒掉了呢
He was the town drunk.
谁说的啊
Who told you that?
他自己...
Bobby Singer.
大家提高警惕
Stay sharp.
我守着前门
I'll watch the front door.
鲍比  你要是不想来  我也理解...
You know, Bobby, if you want to sit this one out...
废话少说  要走快走
Let's just get going.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
你没事吧  迪恩
Dean?
迪恩
Dean!
搭把手
Little help here?
-你还好吧  - 我没事
- That's fine. - Yeah. Fine.
还有弹药吗  我快空仓了
Got any more ammo? I'm low.
够用是够用
Yeah, we got plenty.
只是得绕过那些僵尸
Just run back past the zombies.
我都留在那车里了
It's in the van, where we left it.
你直接说没有不就得了
A simple "No" Would have been fine.
僵尸们到底来这干什么
What are they all doing here, anyway?!
我想我应该知道
I think I get it. What?
这可不妙
Oh, that ain't good.
没子弹了
I'm out.
-我也是  - 来吧
- Me too. - Come on!
这群僵尸也太多了吧
Kinda of a tightfit, don't you think?
没关系  僵尸很蠢
It's all right. They're idiots.
他们可不会开锁
They can't pick a lock.
你这乌鸦嘴  说啥中啥
Don't you ever get tired of being wrong?
我这不也是为了回来帮你么
I'm making this stuff up as I go.
你抱怨个啥
Sue me.
低头  躲开
Get down!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
应该没有漏网之鱼了
Well, if there's any zombies left out there,
我们搜了个遍
We can't find them.
镇民们怎样
How are the townspeople?
被吓得不轻
Pretty freaked out.
还会留下心理创伤
Hell, traumatized.
有人想告诉媒体
A few of them are calling the papers.
但目前为止还没人信
As far as I can tell, nobody's believed 'em yet.
那你呢
Would you?
你心里好受点了吗
How are you holding up?
所有僵尸都烧了吗
Is that everyone?
还差一个
All but one.
为我的不明之举
So, thinking maybe I should apologize
我该向你们道歉
for losing my head back there.
鲍比
Bobby
我们之间不讲究这些
You don't owe us anything.
我知道我没啥资格谈论爱情  但是...
Hey, look, I don't know squat from Shinola about love, but...
你们至少共度了五天的美好时光
At least you got to spend five days with her, right?
是啊
Right.
但如此一来  我更加心如刀割
Which makes things about a thousand times worse.
她是我一生的挚爱
She was the love of my life.
但偏偏造化弄人  我还得经历多少次肺腑之痛
How many times do I got to kill her?
鲍比  一切都会好起来
Are you gonna be okay, bobby?
孩子们  凯伦告诉了我
You boys should know...
死亡骑士出现的原因
...Karen told me why death was here.
你说什么
What do you mean?
他去南达科他州的远郊墓地
I know why he took a stroll through a cemetery
可不是去随便闲逛的
in the sticks of South Dakota.
他是冲着我来的
He came for me.
为什么这么说
What do you mean, you?
死亡骑士冲我而来
Death came for me.
他让凯伦给我带个口信
He brought Karen back to send me a message.
为什么是你
You? Why you?
因为我一直在帮你们两个小兔崽子
Because I've been helping you, you sons of bitches.
所以你坚持不肯答应路西法  萨姆
I'm one of the reasons you're still saying no to Lucifer, Sam.
所以他想把你搞垮吗
So this was like a hit on your life?
我不知道  他们可能想要我的命
I don't know if they wanted to take my life or...
也可能是灵魂
My spirit.
无论怎样  他们要把我除掉
Either way, they wanted me out of the way.
但是你很坚强
But you're gonna be all right.
你一定能挺过去的吧
Right, Bobby?